teacher
Are you here?
Teacher, is there a new book out?
Uh, I feel sorry for the trees.
I wasn't planning on publishing the book
Why have you never been here before?
I felt like crying when I saw the teacher.
Can't I cry? I lost my husband
There's still a lot of work to be done
What do you have to do?
To that person in life
I didn't do anything for you
why did he die
I really want to know the reason
If you were willing to risk your life for something
I'm going to finish it
When you were alive, Junik
I didn't love you enough
someday
I thought I could open my heart
To that extent, Mr. Junik
Because it was warm and friendly
I just go
All I had to do was sit next to him.
Peace and unification are
It's really hard even for married couples
From Junik’s call list
I saw your phone number.
Have you met, teacher?
Uh, it's been over a month.
a friend in the united states
I read the letter you sent
For me, unification is
we can choose
I thought it was an option
Now I see we are all
I was sitting on a bomb called war
Unification is like death
No matter how much I try to avoid it
someday
I was going to have to face it.
What I need to know
There are many, sir.
please teach me
and to me
After entering the camp
unification policy
I asked you to take charge of it.
Did you agree?
Anyway
I kind of like the New Republican Party...
But teacher
Where do you think you're going?
Are you moving?
uh
to Argentina
My relative has a farm.
Argentina?
I am to Father Yang Inbo.
I introduced Junik.
But they
Peace and unification
Because I spoke
He died so violently
People in this country
I love hate more than peace
I love factions and divisions.
I'm no longer in this place
I don't want to live
teacher
I'm planning to run for president.
First time in Korea
When to start working at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs
I want to know anything about North Korea
I went to see the teacher.
I even completed my PhD in the US.
I learned everything from my teacher.
Why is North Korea doing that?
how will it come out
The teacher's understanding and predictions
It was always right
Please help me, teacher.
Moonjuya
North Korea is now
I'm falling apart helplessly
There's a nuclear weapon in it
America has no choice but to intervene
This war will be inevitable
Only willing individuals
under the wheel of history
It will break apart
It's okay to break
Junik and the priest
That's what you did.
If the teacher helps me
the direction of the wheel
Let me spin it a little bit.
How
Did you take that picture?
As soon as I heard the gunshot
I frantically clicked the shutter button.
Suddenly a woman
come into the frame
I was surprised
Who on earth is that woman?
How to do it at gunpoint
How can you be so bold?
So
She shot her husband just seconds ago.
In front of terrorists, with my bare body.
Yes, this week’s hot topic is
Former Ambassador to the United Nations Seo Moon-joo
I am the widow of the late Rep. Jang Jun-ik.
Look at those eyes now
That courage and anger
Even in such extreme situations
No embarrassment
Those words go around
'My wife should have appeared in the election'
‘Then I will film it right away.’
If in the current situation
If former Ambassador Seo runs for office
Which party is it?
I am a member of the New Republican Party
I think I should go
Her husband, Rep. Jang Jun-ik
We must inherit the political legacy.
Only then will running for office be meaningful.
However, former Ambassador Seo Moon-joo
A symbolic greeting from the Chae Kyung-shin administration.
As the face representing the Chae government
It has been considered
Our Junik
To throw him out of the primary
I know you did your best, Mr.
The late Rep. Jang Jun-ik
He was a valuable asset to our party.
Thanks to our supporters
I have become much younger
But that's it.
There are things we can change
There is something that is missing
What is anti-communism?
It can't be changed
On the blood shed while crossing the 38th line
Our party is standing
A candidate who doesn't understand that
It's impossible to get elected.
So
Are you happy? The day my son died
Why, why are you like this, Chairman?
September 2015
Santa Barbara, California
drunk person driving a car
There was an incident where someone rushed into a bar.
two people die
Three people were seriously injured.
in the field
Two Koreans were arrested
with a local masseuse
Dispatched to the United States for overseas training
Prosecutor Jang Jun-sang
This is a woman I met by chance at a bar.
I feel like I'm being sexually harassed
I tried to help
Suddenly I got angry
He ran to the car
I was not indicted due to insufficient evidence.
Evidence that wasn't there at the time
What if now?
When my husband died, he told me
I left a cabinet with many drawers.
It's funny
I've been in politics for so long
All that's left is a dresser
There
There is also a drawer with the CEO's name written on it.
When I opened it, there were a lot of interesting things...
Today
I chose this
How come you’re so bungeoppang?
It would be unreasonable to say no
It's been over 20 years
People in politics at that time
There were all children out of wedlock.
He said he drove
Speaking of which, that woman
I don't remember a thing
It's been a while
I spoke to my sister-in-law.
He said he would be willing to testify.
I tried to keep quiet because of the kids.
A violent husband is running for president
I can't stand it
You're mom, right?
Did your mom take your sister-in-law’s side?
What about Ambassador Seo Moon-ju?
Even when he was ambassador to the United Nations
The external evaluation was very good.
Plus, she's a woman.
female leaders around the world
Because it’s the trend, now
leave
Studying abroad in Germany
If you say you're going to see the kids
There's nothing strange about it.
Mom is always like this
always me
Make me feel like a dump
Tell my mom
Now that it's like this
Let's all meet in hell
Sister-in-law, please know too.
When I return from my trip
There's no way to come empty-handed
When it's revealed
In the 6th month as party leader
My political life is over.
I
I've been curious about this for a long time
Why should I trust you to destroy my son?
Does this person and that person walk around holding hands?
When you come to my house to say New Year's greetings
He was someone who couldn't even sit on the floor.
What can I do for you
Would you like it?
Junsang is
I'm going to take a flight to Germany today.
My daughter-in-law will run for office.
On the road in front of my daughter-in-law
Don't be an obstacle
From a diplomat background
Expertise in government administration
There are also times of doubt.
Among our past presidents
President Choi Kyu-ha
I had a diplomat background.
Korea
Because it is a country caught between powerful countries.
- Diplomacy is a matter of survival.
- That's right.
I love that kid
I'll make it an event
The incident is getting bigger and bigger
It will become a phenomenon
and soon
It will become a myth
Hello, CEO.
Ambassador Seo Moon-joo is a member of the New Republican Party.
Is it true that you are running in the primary?
Ambassador Seo Moon-joo
How to do it
The will of the late Rep. Jang Jun-ik
Can we spread the word to the world?
I know that's exactly what you're thinking.
Actually, I am
It is the one that receives the most criticism within the party.
Why faster, Ambassador?
Can't you bring me?
The party's primary election schedule is...
Ambassador Seo said to the late Rep. Jang,
Do you think you can achieve your goal?
Selection team, test results there
Report any abnormalities
Contact network of competent authorities there
check it carefully
And if there is something that doesn't cooperate
contact me
And where is the hospital?
This is Yeo Mi-ji, the office manager.
Yes, three people?
Candidate
Yesterday at six institutions
New Republican presidential candidate
An emergency opinion poll was conducted.
In all results, the candidate
It is surprisingly ranked 1st and 2nd.
Wow, outside
Do you know what's going on outside?
How did you know this phone number?
I want to be an election campaigner
The phone, the phone...
Wow! This is enough
In technical terms, they say this:
torn
‘Teared it’?
My form is crazy!
Well, what's crazy?
Has Anderson been contacted?
Ah...
I'm trying several channels.
I can't contact you
I finally found my sister's contact information yesterday.
I'll let you know as soon as I get the answer.
No, I'll contact you directly.
And Mr. Midge
keep telling me
There's an email coming
Take a look at the contents yourself
Can you check?
I'll forward it to you
yes, i understand
Rep. Jang's computer and laptop
Decrypt your phone
I tried restoring the deleted log.
Several times on a secure mail site
We found your access record.
server in switzerland
It's an encrypted email service.
Even the FBI can't access it
It is known as mail service.
People who send and receive this email
fifteen digits each
Share the encryption key
Is there any way to find out?
This thin sear mail is
Because the level of difficulty is so high...
I'll try to solve it
I think it's hard to tell
Are you in a meeting?
I can't call you anymore
Where did I put my cell phone?
I got so many calls
in the name of an aide
make one more
Everyone does that
we are doing well
It smells like politicians will do well
The first thing I take on is
They are people with money
to you somehow
People are going crazy trying to make donations.
I didn't do anything special.
Until now, I turned on the lights and played music.
Now that you have appeared
I need to show a performance
Debut is always flashy
First, let’s start with the triple axel.
Can I do a triple axel?
this sunday
At Gwanghwamun Square
I'm going to declare candidacy.
We're going to gather a lot of people.
The organization does not use
The public knows you as Joan of Arc
to protect my husband
A woman standing in front of a gun with her bare body
Just like that
make people
I need to make you cry for me
The simplest way is
at the right time
you're crying
I don't think I can do it
Do you really want to be president?
without crying in public
No one ever became president
that's your best
Precious and fragile part
It means I opened it and showed it to you.
how much of that moment
Can you make it honestly?
It's up to you
That will be your triple axel
Veteran speech writer
I wrote a draft of my speech.
Where should I shed tears?
Because I marked it
Master it before Sunday comes
Representative?
The head of the National Intelligence Service called.
Why?
The US movement is unusual.
In line with the declaration of candidacy
I heard a lot of American kids came in.
Who? Is it the CIA?
Not only that
Candidate may be dangerous
“Valkyrie Group Mercenary Contract”
cheers
Bring it
‘Red Feather’ Billy Gray
I came to Seoul yesterday
I have intelligence
do something in front of the camera
They said they were planning to show it to me.
we still
I feel them as brothers
The recent North Korean human rights report
It was so heartbreaking
In the distant future we
When I look back on what I did today
just like us
Deserving of a human life
For the people of North Korea
I hope I can say I did the right thing
I sincerely hope
Hello?
Are you still sleeping?
What's going on?
Who will run for president
Will I use it if I sleep at this time?
If you have something to say, say it.
If you wanted to surprise me
Success
Honestly, I feel like I got slapped.
It's fresh
I can face this much
I didn't even think of it as a bowl.
I know
Whether he becomes president or not
I'm not interested, just
I have plans during my term.
I said
To prevent war
I would do anything
If you get in my way I'll hit you
I wanted to tell you in advance
Because I liked you
I didn't mean to startle you.
I had no intention of fighting back.
Just
Mr. President
I don't think I can do it
I can't stop the war
You think you can stop it?
Rep. Jang's death
You said it should be handled diplomatically.
A chance to hop in an American car
no
That's us
This is your chance to access the truth
Diplomacy that is not based on truth
In the end it fails
But
Do you know this?
In Korea
Those whom the United States does not tolerate
That I can't be president
Those people
They say they don't want you to become president
Take care of yourself
I'm telling you because I'm genuinely worried.
Today is going to be a long day
Starting from Gwangju
Until arriving in Seoul
Your journey...
one in itself
Because I have to declare my candidacy
how many people
Did you see how many people came?
I would like to commemorate Rep. Jang.
All of this process
Through SNS and live broadcasting
It will be broadcast
Preface!
Symbol number 2 preface!
S One, have you secured a candidate drop-off point?
Yes, the drop-off point has been secured.
Okay, check the entry route.
Check if there is anything special
Came in with Billy Gray
The identity of the Korean man has been determined.
His name is Dustin Hyun.
He's a bomb technician from Caltech.
Do you know what?
I've been there for a long time
I dreamed of a scene like this
This is the moment when a candidate enters politics.
maybe today
best of my life
I think it will be a day
Those who made today's Republic of Korea
those stories
Still vivid sadness
It was a time I could hold in my heart.
I will now leave for Seoul
Now at Gwanghwamun Square
Already
There are many supporters gathered
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it well.
hello
You've been waiting a long time, right?
Aren’t you having a hard time?
are you okay!
thank you
I need to speak to candidate Seo Moon-ju.
Who are you?
I need to call you right now
It's an emergency
It's him at the cathedral, right?
Candidate Seo Moon-ju
You can't take that train now.
Yes, me, candidate.
This is Director Changhee.
Yes, manager.
Get off the train, Seo Moon-ju.
You can't sit down
Don't sit down!
Seo Moon-ju
Baek San-ho?
listen to me carefully
From now on
You can't get up from your seat.
Do you understand?
What do you mean?
never
Just like I'm sitting now
Don't move.
PD, broadcast
I think I need to stop for a moment.
A person who just had his seat repaired
Look for it
Mr. Midge
They say there is no such employee.
If the seat is broken
They say the train will be repaired after its operation is over.
My name is White Coral
Since 2007, as a special security force
I worked in Iraq
There, they plant bombs on chairs.
Terrorism is common
Do you think you'll explode when you wake up?
If it were a pressure-release bomb, that would be the case.
If it's a time limit device
It will explode at a certain time.
Report it to the police first
Yes, I will do it.
Where is the next station?
Asan Station
-What's the next station?
- It's light.
Let's meet there.
leave for a moment
Please wait a moment
who came
I went to repair the chair.
In railway construction
They said there was no such person.
In Iraq, in such cases
A bomb must have been planted...
Reporter
This is Korea.
Not Iraq
The police will come to Gwangmyeong Station.
I'm on my way now.
You will arrive at Gwangmyeong Station in 50 minutes.
This is special room number 3.
For now, here
Just convince people
Can you send it to another compartment?
Let's try it
What's going on?
There's less than an hour left
Bring me here somehow
I will solve it and tell you.
Oh, that crazy bastard.
Are you okay?
yes
It's the police
Please turn off the surrounding power.
all the people
Please evacuate us from the station.
Is the bomb squad on its way?
Ah, ah...
I think it will take 10 more minutes
I will get off quickly
due to train safety issues
I'll check it out in a moment, okay.
come this way
Please move to the previous row
Come this way, yes
I'm breathing too fast
Yes?
When too much oxygen is supplied
I feel dizzy
simple structure
It's a pressure-release bomb.
There is also a time limit set.
How much is left?
6 minutes
look at me
The more urgent my mission is, the more urgent it is
Do everything slowly
Now we
We're having a normal conversation.
beer
If we get out of here safely
From cold beer
I'll just have one drink
now
Mr. Moonju is with me.
I'm going to change places
And I'm leaving this train
I'll be here too
There are people waiting
I hope Moonju comes back
No, not since the baby died.
I have no one
From now on
I do what I do.
It won't be difficult at all
I'll be out soon
- Come back out!
- Candidate, it's dangerous!
Police testified at the scene and
Based on analysis of CCTV inside the train
Mr. Hyun, a man in his 40s
designated as a suspect
They plan to continue the investigation.
revealed
Explosives on train seats
It was found to have been installed.
The suspect is
Have you been identified?
We're still tracking it.
I will tell you gradually
Then who is it?
You don't know yet?
First of all, people here
Everyone go to each other
Write a statement
May I ask you a favor?
Cancel the remaining schedule.
After the police investigation is over
Take your time
It looks good too.
Holding an event
It may seem unreasonable
Because safety is the top priority...
Manager, what do you think?
The candidate decides.
On-site safety
We are securing it without hesitation
Ah...
Let's go
There are still safety issues later.
I prepared thoroughly today
I know and
If you please accompany me
Complete your schedule safely
Go straight to the police station
I think I can go out
Yes, I will proceed with that in mind.
I
I will go with the candidate.
yes
yes we are now
I'm moving to the square.
The declaration of candidacy will proceed as scheduled.
Yes, I think it will take about 20 minutes.
Now, watch your step.
backstage
You have arrived
He's going up right away.
Candidate has arrived
All waiting
Are you sure you can do this?
It was cold, but many people waited.
Why don't you take some rest?
You must be very nervous in front of people.
I stand in front of people
I've never been nervous
on both sides of the podium
You will see a prompter.
don't worry
Everyone
Candidate Seo Moon-joo
Please give us a round of applause!
- Just a moment.
-Keep your distance
You can't come in.
Check if you have anything in your hands
It's okay
thank you
Tonight, people who don't know me
I think there are a lot.
Also, Rep. Jang Jun-ik’s
Only as a widow
Many of you probably know this.
hello
My name is Seo Moon-ju.
Today I went from Gwangju to Daejeon.
came to this place
The warm hospitality of the people
With a desire for peace
I came to this place
But I
It seems like it came from further away
Director, the content is completely different.
Shall the teleprompter stop?
no, no
First of all, keep it afloat
in front of the desk
Put up the Taegeukgi
From the United States where I studied
My husband, Rep. Jang Jun-ik
With the wish for peace and unification
While experiencing death due to injustice,
And just now
sitting on a bomb and riding a train
I'm heading here
I kept running
That bomb is
from what
Was he trying to stop me?
I'm heading towards you
I was on my way
Some people
I am traditional
Regardless of political affiliation
Because she is a female diplomat
He said he couldn't become president
Some other people
At my late husband's party
Because I'm running for office
They say he shouldn't be president
Some other people
I'm abroad
Because I lived a long time
Korea
When you say you can't represent
That's why you
I'm in our politics
that it can bring about fundamental change
Embracing different points
We can achieve great unification
Weak and neglected
For the forgotten
I could become president
Because you trusted me
You guys are experiencing that kind of change.
Hope for unity and peace
me today
What were you trying to hold on to?
i don't know
But
without fear of anything
Without stopping even for a moment
I will run towards that hope
peaceful street
happy family
people who have each other
And safely
Drinking at the end of the day
for a glass of beer
All of this forever
to keep the peace
Now I
Running for the 22nd Presidential Election of the Republic of Korea
I declare
Preface!
Preface! Preface!
Congratulations
A superstar is born
I jumped, triple axel.
Did you see it?
You tore it
Every night in my dreams
I walked as lightly as a blade of grass
dying is
I wasn't afraid
But I didn't know
someone's hand
That you were supporting me
What about the candidate?
The investigation isn't over yet.
- Huh? Coming out
- He's coming out.
Candidate, let’s go.
White coral seed
Was it hard today?
Are your legs okay?
Just a little scratched, okay?
What should I be thankful for?
I don't know
By the way, Baek San-ho
I still don't understand today
How to do it at the right time
Are you there again, this time?
Rep. Jang Jun-ik dies
The priest passed away
Next is
I thought it was Seo Moon-ju
Because I inherited Rep. Jang’s will.
If a bomb exploded today
He would have been fatally injured.
someone
I was trying to convey this message
Anyone who tries to stop war
That it would be like this
Probably Mr. Moonju
It will continue to be dangerous.
I will strengthen our security team.
Your security team won't be able to do it.
I renewed my contract with Valkyrie.
Seo Moon-ju more than me
A person who can protect himself well
None
hire me
As a personal bodyguard
How can I trust Baek San-ho?
Let's investigate
battles i participated in
The roles I played
We also monitor if necessary.
Why do you want to do this?
Seo Moon-ju wants to prevent war.
Me too
To me
There is an assignment left by the priest.
Do you think I can do it?
I had a dream
In my dream I
I thought I could do it
When I was Mr. Moonju
But you'll need my help.
Our team members are meticulous and thorough.
They will probably verify it persistently.
Getting things done
I wish they were fast people
Understand that I am the boss
unconditionally on command
Can you follow along?
unable to obey orders
There are no soldiers
However, in emergency situations
You must obey me immediately
I'm the boss then
Okay, Baek San-ho.
Please take care of me
thank you
Candidate